jadopado.com 2011-12-24

# Privacy Policy / JadoPado

**The Gist**  
Your privacy is extremely important to us. We won't ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (When we do ask for your information it is usually to ensure that we're dealing with real people and not a bot!). We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights. 

If you have questions about accessing or correcting your personal data please get in touch with us through any of the ways listed at the JadoPado Help site.

It is JadoPado's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.

Our Privacy Policy is a part of our general Terms of Service and has been extracted for your convenience.

**Website Visitors**  
Like most website operators, JadoPado collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. JadoPado’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how JadoPado’s visitors use its website. From time to time, JadoPado may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

JadoPado also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users. JadoPado only discloses logged in user IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**  
Certain visitors to JadoPado’s websites choose to interact with JadoPado in ways that require JadoPado to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that JadoPado gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with JadoPado are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, JadoPado collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfil the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with JadoPado. JadoPado does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**  
JadoPado may collect statistics about the behaviour of visitors to its website. For instance, JadoPado may monitor the most popular products on the website. JadoPado may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, JadoPado does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**  
JadoPado discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organisations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on JadoPado’s behalf or to provide services available at JadoPado’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of these employees, contractors and affiliated organisations may be located outside of your home country; by using JadoPado’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. JadoPado will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organisations, as described above, JadoPado discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena or court order, or when JadoPado believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of JadoPado, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of the website and have supplied your email address, JadoPado may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with JadoPado and our products which will primarily be on our blog.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. JadoPado uses cookies to help JadoPado identify and track visitors, their usage of JadoPado's website, and their website access preferences. JadoPado visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using JadoPado’s website, with the drawback that certain features of JadoPado’s website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Ads**  
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognise your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by JadoPado and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
